Guide to the Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated RL.11128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 2002-2012 and undated; 12
  - Originals, 2002-2012 and undated; 99
    - Walmart and Procter & Gamble Operation Family Connect, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-289)
    - Chevron and DonorsChoose Fuel Your School videos, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-290)
    - Oshkosh B'Gosh Cranes for Kids, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-291)
    - Sears Heroes at Home: A Hero's Song, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-292)
    - Maytag Faces of Dependability video, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-293)
    - World Vision's End Malaria Campaign, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-294)
    - Blue Angels Mission for Toys for Tots, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-295)
    - Friends Forever, Did You Know?, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-296)
    - Kohl National Volunteers Go Green Week, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-297)
    - Kohl's Blanket Milwaukee Pink viral video, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-298)
    - Downy Touch of Comfort Program, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-299)
    - Kohl's Blanket Milwaukee Pink viral video, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-300)
    - Kohl's and American Cancer Society Live Pink Ribbon viral video, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-301)
    - Kohl National Volunteers Go Green Week, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-302)
    - Choice Hotels Music, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-303)
    - Weeding Out Hunger, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-304)
    - Macy's Wear Red Quicktime :15, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-305)
    - Honeywell FMA Live! Introductory video, 2005 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-306)
    - Honeywell FMA Live! press highights, 2005 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-307)
    - Weight Watchers Lose for Good PSA featuring Jenny McCarthy and post campaign b-roll, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-308)
    - Weight Watchers Lose for Good videos, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-309)
    - CNN Fit Nation sizzle reel, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-310)
    - Phonak Hear the World highlights video, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-311)
    - Phonak Hear the World View from the Bay ABC-7 News, Sirius Radio, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-312)
    - CYBEX Pink Ribbon Run marketing materials, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-313)
    - CYBEX Pink Ribbon Run registration, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-314)
    - Kohl's Cares Supporting Women's Health, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-315)
    - Kohl's Cares Announcing Our Initiative to Help Fight Breast Cancer, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-316)
    - Kohl's and American Cancer Society Launch of Women's Health Platform, 2010 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-317)
    - Kohl's Building Healthy Habits :30, 2010 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-318)
    - World Vision's End Malaria Campaign, 2010 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-319)
    - NFL/American Cancer Society, A Crucial Catch, 2012 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-320)
    - Sounds of Pertussis campaign media clips, 2012 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-321)
    - Own It campaign video case story, 2012 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-322)
    - Own It campaign Adam Levine :60 broadcast PSA, 2012 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-323)
    - Dishing with the Co-Stars, 2012 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-324)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs Johnny Damon Ynet, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-325)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs Boston Coverage, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-326)
    - Luxaire/Make-a-Wish partnership overview, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-327)
    - Luxaire/Make-a-Wish Special Delivery TV spots, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-328)
    - Designs of Hope Houston event recap video, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-329)
    - Hope Lives Here, UNICEF's campaign against AIDS campaign video 8:33, 2004 June (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-330)
    - VMS Auction at Crowne Plaza Times Square Steve and Vicky Morning Show WSTR-FM Atlanta 23:15, 2005 Aug. (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-331)
    - Lee National Denim Day media highlights, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-332)
    - Procter & Gamble/UNICEF disc 1, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-333)
    - Procter & Gamble/UNICEF disc 2, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-334)
    - Soraya, Por Ser Quien Sou/No One Else psa's in Spanish and English, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-335)
    - Safe Kids Week artwork, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-336)
    - Safe Kids Week artwork SKN-6254, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-337)
    - Bounty Cards that Count creative TV and radio, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-338)
    - Hard Rock Café/Leary Firefighters Foundation Firefighters Eat Free at Hard Rock Cafes Worldwide, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-339)
    - Hard Rock Café/Leary Firefighters Foundation Firefighters Eat Free at Hard Rock Cafes Worldwide, FOX Good Day New York aired 7/11, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-340)
    - Glad to Help sample TV coverage DSNY, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-341)
    - Glad to Help sample TV coverage Mardi Gras, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-342)
    - Channel Red Salvation Army spot :15, 20060 Nov. 10 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-343)
    - Holland America On Deck for the Cure, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-344)
    - Yoplait Champions information, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-345)
    - Nick Federoff on Gardening; Pat Simpson, 2002 Mar. 2 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-346)
    - Clorox Fresh Step materials, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-347)
    - Lee National Denim Day logos, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-348)
    - CIBC World Markets, Miracle Day, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-349)
    - National Kids' Day wrap report and highlights, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-350)
    - We Are Goodwill 8:34, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-351)
    - Fireman's Fund, Heritage in the News clips, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-352)
    - Into the Fire, film by Bill Couturié, 2006 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-353)
    - Into the Fire, film by Bill Couturié, critics' cut, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-354)
    - St. Jude's Children's Hospital Thanks and Giving spot :15, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-355)
    - Colgate-Palmolive Healthy Bedtime Habits news segments, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-356)
    - CDC, Ninos Activos, Familias Sanas, end of the tour, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-357)
    - PNC/Sesame Street Elmo Happy Healthy Ready for School 22:00, 2004 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-358)
    - DoubleTree Teaching Kids to Care, 2004 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-359)
    - VW/Scholastic "Developing Your Powers of Persuasion" materials, 2004 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-360)
    - Who Wants to Be a Superhero? Episode 204, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-361)
    - Rally for the Cure, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-362)
    - MVParents Advocates Toolkit, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-363)
    - MVParents Advertising/PR creative, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-364)
    - Walgreen Hope Blooms with You AWARE talk radio, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-365)
    - Princeton Partners Race for the Cure, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-366)
    - Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope program overview, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-367)
    - Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope PR summary, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-368)
    - VERB Anytour movie, 2004 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-369)
    - VERB Anytour photos, 2004 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-370)
    - Cook for the Cure Komen conference, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-371)
    - IAMS Home 4 the Holidays media coverage, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-372)
    - Cartoon Network Rescuing Recess; Get Animated PSAs, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-373)
    - Cartoon Network Rescuing Recess highlight reel, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-374)
    - GSN the Network for Games, National Vocabulary Championship sizzle, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-375)
    - Win with Words PSAs and National Vocabulary Championship spots, 2006 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-376)
    - RH Donnelley Recycle for Teachers, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-377)
    - Hyubndai Hope on Wheels, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-378)
    - Backpacker Magazine's Summit for Someone benefit climb program overview, 2006 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-379)
    - Greater Chicago Food Depository, Hunger Knows No Season marketing materials, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-380)
    - Coldstone Creamery/Make-a-Wish World's Largest Ice Cream Social media clips, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-381)
    - Blockbuster/Boys and Girls Clubs of America hi res photos, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-382)
    - Wal-Mart Healthy Ogres Eat 5 a Day the Color Way, 2004 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-383)
    - Domino's Pizza Delivers Incredible Wishes, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-384)
    - Elefanten Steps to Art, concert footage and images, 2002 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-385)
    - Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope, TRT 9:00, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-386)
    - Hiefer Hope Blend, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-387)
    - Yoplait Built Differently to Perform Better, 2003 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-388)
    - Quilted Northern Komen Foundation Sponsorship, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-389)
    - Quilted Northern Komen Foundation Sponsorship, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-390)
    - Quilted Northern Komen Foundation Sponsorship, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-391)
    - Lunafest trailer, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-392)
    - Safe Cosmetics Campaign, 2006 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-393)
    - Breast Cancer 3-Day Changing Lives, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-394)
    - Breast Cancer 3-Day Media relations results, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-395)
    - AT&T Paperless Program supporting materials, 2005 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-396)
    - Center for Companies that Care supporting materials, 2007 (Box AV7, Dvd RL11030-DVD-397)
    - Home Depot Month of Service TRT 5:04, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-398)
    - Gibson Music Rising EPK, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-399)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs Day for Kids wrap video, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-400)
    - JC Penney Jam Concert for America's Kids, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-401)
    - JC Penney CBS First Gift Afterschool, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-402)
    - Whirlpool Reba "Key" commercials :60 and :30, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-403)
    - Whirlpool Reba "Key" commercials :60 and :30, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-404)
    - ChoicePoint ADAM external video, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-405)
    - Meals on Wheels Mayor's Support Slideshow, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-406)
    - Lunafest trailer, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-407)
    - Safe Cosmetics Campaign, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-408)
    - RE/MAX Children's Miracle Network, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-409)
    - RE/MAX Home is Where the Hearst Is, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-410)
    - First Book Highlights, 2003 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-411)
    - Marshmallow Peeps Fun Bus Tour recap video, 2004 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-412)
    - KitchenAid Halo images, 2003 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-413)
    - Rosie the Riveter World War II Home Front National Historical Park media kit, 2004 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-414)
    - Urban Advantage Network 10 PSAs, 2002 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-415)
    - Urban Advantage Network 10 PSAs, 2002 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-416)
    - Closing the Health Gap demo of PSAs and spots, 2002 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-417)
    - American Heart Association Food Certification Program: 5 Nutrition Tips spots, 2003 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-418)
    - March of Dimes Premature Birth "My Son" English PSA :60 and :30, 2003 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-419)
    - March of Dimes Premature Birth "My Son" Spanish PSA :60 and :30, 2003 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-420)
    - March of Dimes Premature Birth "My Son" African American PSA :60 and :30, 2003 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-421)
    - Target/Tiger Woods Start Something teacher's guide, 2003 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-422)
    - Dress for Success Suits to Self Sufficiency, 2008 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-423)
    - World Hunger Relief Week PR highlights 3:40, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-424)
    - World Hunger Relief Week direct mailer disk, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-425)
    - National Wildlife Federation Backyard Habitat TV loop, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-426)
    - Rose/Glenn Group We Love this Place! Signs the movie, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-427)
    - Make a Wish: Natalie F.'s Wish, 2004 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-428)
    - Target/Tiger Woods Start Something teacher's guide, 2004 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-429)
    - Red Sky Go On Campaign, 2009 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-430)
    - IAMS Home 4 the Holidays sizzle reel, 2009 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-431)
    - IAMS Home 4 the Holidays press materials, 2009 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-432)
    - Jumpstart Laura Bush PSA, Matt Lauer video, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-433)
    - 9 Lives Morris' Million Cat Rescue, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-434)
    - Microsoft/UNHCR ninemillion.org, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-435)
    - Bounty Cards that Count creative TV and radio, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-436)
    - Esquire House 360 press clips, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-437)
    - Showtime Barbershop Rationale, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-438)
    - Prostate Net Confronting Prostate Cancer Know Your Options, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-439)
    - Hollywood Video Community Spotlight Training Manual DVD, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-440)
    - Hollywood Video in-store monitor video, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-441)
    - Philadephia Hollywood Video Starlight site dedication, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-442)
    - Intro for Philly Starlight Site, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-443)
    - Starlight Site TV coverage, ABC-TV, WPVI, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-444)
    - Boost Mobile RockCorps, 2006 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-445)
    - Boost Mobile RockCorps Got 2 Give 2 Get episode 101 (25:45)-102 (23:45)-103 (22:33), 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-446)
    - Boost Mobile RockCorps Got 2 Give 2 Get episode 104, 23:49, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-447)
    - Boost Mobile RockCorps Racio City Concert 41:49, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-448)
    - Team Gold's Tour de Cure recruitment/promotional reel, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-449)
    - Cure, Care, Commitment Meets Life Changing Results sample broadcast media coverage, 2006 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-450)
    - Major League Baseball/Habitat for Humanity logo, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-451)
    - Pedigree Adoption Drive 2006 Press, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-452)
    - Pedigree Adoption Drive PSAs 1:15, 2007 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-453)
    - Learn and Serve: An Introduction to Service Learning, undated (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-454)
    - Procter & Gamble Downy Touch of Comfort full piece and :30 spot, undated (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-455)
    - Procter & Gamble Downy Touch of Comfort full piece and :30 spot, undated (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-456)
    - Samsung's Hope for Education Halo Awards Submission, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-457)
    - Samsung's Hope for Education Harold Hechler Photography digital images, 2004 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-458)
    - Samsung's Hope for Education, 2005 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-459)
    - Schwab Learning "Fridge"; SparkTop "Team Spark" spots, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-460)
    - Schwab Learning "Fridge"; SparkTop "Team Spark" spots, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-461)
    - Social Security Administration Ticket to Work, 2005 (Box AV10, Dvd RL11030-DVD-462)
    - OfficeMax A Day Made Better 3:08, 2010 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-463)
    - Scholastic Book Clubs Classrooms Care Reading is Giving presentation, 2009 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-464)
    - Macy's Million Reasons to Believe print summary October 2008-January 2009 (Box AV9, Dvd RL11030-DVD-465)
    - Macy's Million Reasons to Believe sizzle reel, 2009 (Box AV9, Dvd RL11030-DVD-466)
    - VH1 Save the Music Foundation/Procter & Gamble on air promotion, 2006 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-001)
    - Warm Coats & Warm Hearts Drive final, 2008 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-002)
    - Albertson's Healthy Eaters interactive field trip 7:31, 2008 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-003)
    - Home Safety Council, Code Red Rover Grownup Come Over, 2006 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-004)
    - Avon Let's Talk Beauty Tour, 2006 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-005)
    - Cat in the Hat/First Book, Cat Challenge TRT 2:24, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-006)
    - Liz Claiborne No More tour coverage, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-007)
    - BMW Ultimate Drive, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-008)
    - Women's International Bowling Congress Bowl for the Cure, TRT 5:39, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-009)
    - Hershey's Kissmobile Tour highlights, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-010)
    - Entemann's Por un barrio mejor, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-011)
    - Sephora/Operation Smile, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-012)
    - Lee Jeans Get in Gear Bike Safety video TRT 5:52, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-013)
    - UPS Store, Deliver Some Love, Toys for Tots Campaign, 2005 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-014)
    - The Great Safety Adventure, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-015)
    - Space Needle Tackling Hurricane Relief news coverage, 2005 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-016)
    - Georgia-Pacific/Ronald McDonald House Quilted Northern 100th Anniversary Highlights, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-017)
    - Procter & Gamble/UNICEF, SMT Gear Up for Fall, Downy UNICEF TV, Sabado Gigante, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-018)
    - Yoplait Save Lids to Save Lives Program, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-019)
    - Things Remembered/Make-a-Wish Holiday television, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-020)
    - Race for the Cure program recap video, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-021)
    - Race for the Cure Hope on Broadway recap video, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-022)
    - Lee National Denim Day media highlights, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-023)
    - Race for the Cure program recap video, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-024)
    - Angel Soft Angels in Action video, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-025)
    - Briggs & Stratton National Mower Tune-Up Month, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-026)
    - Weather Channel Rays Awareness Campaign, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-027)
    - Johnson & Johnson Safe Kids Campaign; All That; Are You Forgetting Something?, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-028)
    - National Safe Kids Week media clips, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-029)
    - Ford Blue Oval Certified Commitment to Kids PSA "Most Important Photo" :25/5, 2002 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-030)
    - Ford Blue Oval Certified Commitment to Kids PR clips, 2002 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-031)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop, Nikki's Bear Tour Spring 2003 results; Stuffed with Hugs results (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-032)
    - Sprint Yellow Pages Recycle for Literacy 5:37, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-033)
    - American Idol Season 2, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-034)
    - American Idol edited, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-035)
    - Stop & Shop Triple Winner Video 7:40, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-036)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop, Operation Stuffed with Hugs, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-037)
    - AXA Achievement TRT 6:43, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-038)
    - California Nutrition Network, Paper Dolls :30, School Daze :30, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-039)
    - Pearson-Jumpstart Partnership Promo Video 8:08, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-040)
    - Whirlpool/Habitat for Humanity, Key :60, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-041)
    - VH1 Save the Music Foundation Electronic Press Kit, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-042)
    - PNC Grow Up Great shareholder version 2:44, 2004 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-043)
    - DoubleTree Teaching Kids to CARE, 2004 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-044)
    - HSBC Your Credit Counts: Olmos TV interview; Rashad interview, 2004 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-045)
    - Nextel, Phoenix Coyotes Red Cross PSA, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-046)
    - History Channel Save Our Sounds, 1998 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-047)
    - Hollywood Video TV news coverage, TRT 11:21, 2002-2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-048)
    - Hollywood Video and Starlight United Airlines ad, :90, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-049)
    - Introducing Hollywood Video Starlight Site and local news footage, TRT 9:00, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-050)
    - Holiday Video holiday 2003, TRT 120:00 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-051)
    - CIBC Miracle Day employee version, 2002 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-052)
    - Leukemia & Lymphoma Society Days of Our Lives recognition ceremony; Soap Central, Mrs. Fields, Days/Walk episode, TRT 5:13, 2002 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-053)
    - Heifer International, The Promise, TRT 9:52, 1995 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-054)
    - Heifer International, The Promise, TRT 9:52, 1995 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-055)
    - Animal Planet Backyard Habitat TV short and promo, TRT 10:26, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-056)
    - Potawatomi Bingo Casino, Miracle on Canal Street, 2002 Nov. 14 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-057)
    - Potawatomi Bingo Casino, Miracle on Canal Street, 2002 Dec. 19 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-058)
    - Potawatomi Bingo Casino, Miracle on Canal Street, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-059)
    - Potawatomi Bingo Casino, Miracle on Canal Street, Rose, 2002 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-060)
    - Potawatomi Bingo Casino, Miracle on Canal Street, Thank you spot, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-061)
    - Sprint Yellow Pages Recycle for Literacy media clips, TRT 46:35, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-062)
    - Lancome/Girls Inc. partnership launch video, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-063)
    - Hershey's Kissmobile Tour highlights, 2004 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-064)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs PSA campaign with Denzel Washington, School's Out, 2004 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-065)
    - Volkswagen/Scholastic, Fasten Your Seat Belt...Go Far!, 2004 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-066)
    - Domino's Pizza/Make-a-Wish Foundation, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-067)
    - Domino's Pizza/Make-a-Wish Foundation Grants Taylor Benson's Wish, TRT 14:00, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-068)
    - Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope; Main; Arnold Palmer, Magic Johnson, Boomer Esiason, Joe Torre, 2003 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-069)
    - Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope, TRT 9:00, 2003 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-070)
    - ConAgra Foods Child Hunger spots, TRT 8:00, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-071)
    - Verizon Reads Image, 2002 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-072)
    - ABC Cable Network Learning Together PSA w/Julie Andrews :15x2, 2003 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-073)
    - Rosie the Riveter, 2004 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-074)
    - ABC Radio Networks Take a Loved One to the Doctor Day 2:00, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-075)
    - ABC Radio Networks Take a Loved One to the Doctor Day 28:00, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-076)
    - ABC Radio Networks Take a Loved One to the Doctor Day 2:00, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-077)
    - American Heart Association No Place Like Home, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11030-VHS-078)